fulltraffic.net 2011-06-24

# FullTraffic - Privacy Policy

**1\. What personally identifiable information does FullTraffic.Net collect?**

This Privacy Policy covers www.fulltraffic.net treatment of personally identifiable information that is collected by our company when a customer is visiting our site and using our services. This policy also covers FullTraffic's treatment of any personally identifiable information that business partner’s share with our company and added to our Web site database. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that FullTraffic does not own or control, or to people that FullTraffic does not employ or manage.

To place an order on our Web site, a user must first complete an order form. Whilst placing an order, a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have shown as an interest.

Top

**2\. What organization/s collects the information?**

FullTraffic collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site and co-branded partner Web sites. We will not sell, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. When the user signs up for these services, we may share names, or other contact information that is necessary for third parties to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

Top

**3\. With whom FullTraffic.Net may share user information?**

FullTraffic share personal information with third parties who we use to perform functions on our behalf. For example, we use a third party (2CheckOut.com or PayPal) to verify and process your credit card information in order for us to bill you for requested services. All third parties are contractually obligated to use your personal information only for the purpose for which it is given. FullTraffic acts as a reseller for products and services offered on FullTraffic site or on co-branded partner Web sites. Any sharing of personal information with our co-branded partner Web sites occurs only as a direct result of a transaction involving the purchase or free trial of the respective co-branded products or services.

We consider your “personal” contact email as confidential and kept 'entirely private'. We only use your personal email address for our Customer Care representatives and SEO Specialists to send service reports or notifications to you and for some services that requieres.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

Top

**4\. How FullTraffic.Net uses the information?**

First, we use a feature of your browser called a cookie to assign identification to your computer. For the purpose of tracking traffic activity on FullTraffic and its co-branded Web sites, we use a our own, cookie based tracking system. For the purpose of operating our affiliate program and tracking affiliate sales and revenues, we use our own, cookie based tracking system. The unique user ID contained within your cookie automatically identifies your computer, but not you, to our servers every time you visit our site. Cookies by themselves cannot be used to find out the identity of any user but may be correlated with identity information in our log files. You can turn the cookies feature off by using your browser's preference options, but you may not be able to utilize some services properly.

Second, we keep track of your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information about you, such as your location and your Internet service provider. FullTraffic may also collect combined information on how our users are utilizing the site. This might include information regarding traffic patterns through the site and search queries. No IP address/logfile information is tied to Personally Identifiable Information (PII). 

Third, we log browser types, access times, URLs from which visitors came to our site and URLs viewed by visitors while on our site. Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not provide this information to third parties, except in combined form.

Fourth, we post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information such as the customer's name. We do obtain the customer's consent prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial.

Top

**5\. What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?**

We request information from the user on our order forms. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and email address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to process orders. If we have trouble when processing an order, this contact information is used to contact the user.

If you, the customer, indicate that you would like to receive our newsletter, we will use your contact details for sending the newsletter to you only. This information is not distributed to any third-party. You may opt-out from receiving the newsletter by following the instructions in the newsletter. As a customer, you also have the option of updating your email preferences online in the "E-Mail Preferences" section of the account management area.

Top

**6\. What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under FullTraffic.Net control?**

Our Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, that information is protected both online and off-line.

When our order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our accounts department or our Customer Care Representatives, or our SEO Specialists) are granted access to personally identifiable information. ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Our servers that personally identifiable information is stored on are kept in a secure environment and are stored behind a firewall.

If you have any questions about the security at our Web site, you can contact us here.

Top

**7\. How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.**

If your personally identifiable information changes, you may correct or update it by making the change in your account area on the Edit Account page, by contacting us at our Customer Support System, or by contacting us by telephone contact information listed on the Contact page.

Top

**8\. What happens if our Privacy Policy changes?**

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, our users will be notified so they are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we would notify users by way on an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if you have deleted/deactivated your personal information you will not be contacted, nor will your personal information be used in this new manner. We will only use information in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected.

Top

**Questions?**

Contact Us: 

  * Support Ticket System
  * Call Us
  * Send us an E-Mail

Top
